Hello, welcome to the next episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today we are going to
learn I wish or tips. Do
n't be scared by seeing the name, it is a very fun,
very interesting concept. Meaning,
whatever your wishes, imaginations,
dreams or whatever
suggestions you give to others, you
can give all this through this concept. Meaning, for example,
sometimes you all must
remember that dialogue of Amitabh Bachchan from the movie that sometimes a
thought comes to my mind that if you were there, it would have been like this,
you would have done this, you would have done that.
What is this tense? This is neither past tense nor
future tense. If you were there, you would have been there, so with all in
real, it is
not real or when we say that
if I were in your place, I would have done it. I
know for them you do it. I don't
know, but it is said that whether
you were there or not, this is the rear seat.
So, all these situations, we are going to
learn this concept. We are going to
learn five fixed situations from one unit and the good
thing is that  If your simple past tense
concept is clear, if your simple past
tense is clear, if you have not
done it, then watch episode 210, then today we are going to learn a new
section and you will learn all this,
then the connection, first of all let us see
how to do bill, how will we do bill,
how will we say it, so for that
you have to learn a new section, so
watch the description, you know, the
past tense of someone's bill is
warden garden, now you all know that if
you remember episode 210, then because
your homework is like this, when you do
eight more in past tense, you behave normally, what does it
mean, for this, it is
tasty, for this, it is this Gudda, two modes,
woolen
Bollywood, all these, friend, rest up, when we have done it, we will
just
put our fingers on top, it will be wooden and everything else is the same, that
you mean iodine tipsy, this is
against fact, thank you, don't drink
Pepsi, do you understand something, this is
against pizza, obscene, simple ad, rest all are
normal, your section  For them, Dum is simple,
balance, like the weaker section, special contribution has to be
used, it is very simple. Right now you will
see two tables on the screen, if your
simple past tense is clear (episode 210), then
you will recognize them immediately. The first one
is Warn and Hatkar table and the second one is
Mod work. All these sometimes come in the past tense.
We will not go much into this. Now, as
I said, all the Mod words are
used in the past tense. Dum mast.
You have to keep the head of Hattan in the fat. It will be tasty. This will be the
button of similar, not friend. Right now we are going to
use the part for action.
Only among these viral Hat organs, which are
Eastern and Duryodhan, we are going to revolve around them
and what are we going to do with them, Ronit
Ronit is in simple English
because can you give me a par, now you are asking for it, it is on the
basis of girls and you are getting a little
flighty. It turned out that we have become
so used to Islam that he understands that
good past tense is not at all that I am
now we are in the present  It is in tense but you can get
confused it will not be like that in German this
normal past tense total will be
different contest and this is the
contest of most of them, those people will see on advantage and later
first of all how can you do the bill, did you
understand see all the normal and there is
no tension at all B road and Giloy and only
viral hutan and mode all works they have
tense forms only 25 they will get their age
date confirmed understood everyone now
which way do they give its use if
you have understood it completely its use is very interesting first of all it is
very simple user that if someone
wanted to buy a laptop then it would be
issuer diner laptop coupon and then this
viewer paris scarecrow blind copy second is that
and this I said can you give me up in the
funeral in Berlin and a little late you want
10 a little more flu third interesting if you want to give
suggestion to someone but it should not come on your own then
you can ask for it, you
can ask for mask  Later can
I ask I mean
why should you ask in the Duggi test mark courtyard
this way this fact and interesting that I
mean that was my old sir he used to use
kilometer a lot 540 means good also it's
kind of slang it's mainly used
sq meters will go it's good also it
could be that he did
n't call others it could be that his phone is
bad that look you are not for me I can't stay there
someone like this and he doesn't want to talk to home
but he got it could also be
that I called him this you say
that my gas is on the left note shoulder that
it could be like this so how would you say ad
why should I go out dar guide handy and
different factors and till Sanjay and attend
your favorite sometimes that thing would be like so
if I had money
I would go to Paris as long as I had pass then
I would go to Paris so if I had
money left how would I go for this hotel for this
tractor I would go first against
Paris  If you want to send then add it to your side so
its color is this and this and the shop in the Vilas Palace for
₹1 sentence etc. and vanish
clear tubelight and you can it is very simple
what happens with this is that this is a little bit of a high
level concept in this piece also
after the word life you will use this when you
just use it then you are showing
that I can talk about serials, I can
also talk about fiction, it is a tasty concept
important and I find it very
interesting in real life this cancel
okay so very Krishna we device this concept
first of all this action is
used, in the imaginary world that this
can happen, if this happened then to
say all this we use
that how do we bill it is normal and there is
absolutely no tension for it of the villain problem
make such a simple form apply Dubai test against this very
simple rate only mutton viral and
modal verbs they have tense form and 1995
they have free continuous Dashrath clear
And I have used five of them, let's see some cream, first of all I had to
buy a laptop, friend, issue
dryness, laptop coupon, okay, then it is at the
point, don't be angry with me, I am fully, I have
used it, thirdly because I
know how to give advice, I mean,
I can ask for a mask, then
why not test mark the premises, fourthly, it cannot be a
thief, it may be there, then
why enter the app, it is in
handy and effect, that is
and fifthly, my sometimes, if I had
money, it would have been
beneficial for us, the ribbon of Caster Viewers is
absolutely simple, consult, I hope
you have understood this connection, we will meet
in the next episode, thank you